

Aleksandr Russkikh Contact information:

Address:

Ukraine, Kharkov

Phones:

+380678831974, +380661787085

E-mail: aleksandr.russkikh@gmail.com

Skype: alexandr\_russkikh

**Education:** 

2008-2014:

Kharkov National University of

Radioelectronics, Specialist diploma of

"Computer systems analyst".

Online courses and certificates:

SoloLearn: C# Basic

SoloLearn: SQL Basic

SoloLearn: JavaScript Basic

Intuit.ru: Unity Basic

Languages:

Russian - native

Ukrainian - native

English – intermediate reading/writing

English – pre-intermediate speaking

## **Professional Summary:**

Result-oriented QA engineer with over 1,5 years of commercial experience in Web and Mobile testing. Good observation skills and a strong capability of fast learning. Have a thorough knowledge of Functional testing, SDLC, bug life cycle, work with Jira/Redmine and have good communication skills to collaborate with a team.

## **Work Experience:**

**09.2018 – 03.2020:** Speedflow Inc., Manual QA Engineer - Regression testing, executing test cases, bugs reporting and verification, analyzing technical documentation, testing on Windows, Android, and iOS mobile devices, collaborating with the Dev team.

**10.2016 – 02.2018:** KhNURE, Lab Assistant, conducting the laboratory researches on System Software (Programming language C#).

**09.2012 – 08.2016:** KhNURE, Engineer, network administration of the education laboratory.

## **Skills:**

Functional testing:

Smoke/Sanity testing;

Regression testing;

Working with project documentation: creating and support Bug-reports;

API testing (Postman);

Setting up and supporting testing environments;

Working with technical documentation;

Professional Windows OS skills, some Linux OS skills.

Visual Studio 2019 Community

## **Additional Skills:**

SCRUM:

JIRA, Redmine, TestLink;

Writing Technical Documentation (English) Bug reports;

Test Types: Compatibility Testing, Exploratory Testing, Functional Testing, GUI Testing, Mobile Testing.